Question 1. Do you remember the wonderful film on space exploration we watched
together last month?
Sure, it's actually the most impressive one I've seen on that topic.
What do we learn about the speakers?
Question 1. Do you remember the wonderful film on space exploration we watched
together last month?
Sure, it's actually the most impressive one I've seen on that topic.
What do we learn about the speakers?
Question 1. Do you remember the wonderful film on space exploration we watched
together last month?
Sure, it's actually the most impressive one I've seen on that topic.
What do we learn about the speakers?
Question 2. Are you looking for anything in particular?
Yes, my son is graduating from high school and I want to get him something special.
Where does the conversation most probably take place?
Question 2. Are you looking for anything in particular?
Yes, my son is graduating from high school and I want to get him special.
Where does the conversation most probably take place?
Question 3. Mike told me yesterday that he had been looking in vain for a job in the
art gallery. Really?
If I remember right, he had a chance There, but he turned it down.
does the woman say about Mike?
Question 3. Mike told me yesterday that he had been looking in vain for a job in the
art gallery. Really?
If I remember right, he had a to work there, but he turned it down.
What does the woman say about Mike?
Question 4. Would you like to come to Susan's birthday party tomorrow evening?
I'm going to give a lecture tomorrow.
I wish I could be At the same time, does the man mean?
4. you like to come to Susan's birthday party tomorrow evening?
I'm going to give a lecture.